question_data = [
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]



